So something I woke up thinking about was that knowledge is power.
And when you think in a mindset of abundance, that means power is everywhere because knowledge is everywhere.
Meaning you can learn from every person that you interact with.
You can learn tools of inspiration.
You can learn how not to act.
You can learn happiness.
You can learn information.
You can learn through their stories.
You can learn through simply their attitudes.
Like every interaction allows you a space for learning if you come into every interaction with the mindset of that.
And the power you receive from that may not be the power to overthrow anything.
It may not be the power to hold over people, which some people really want.
But it may in fact be the power of understanding yourself, which is a very powerful tool.
Because in a life of uncertainty, being certain of who you are is really all you can hold on to to keep you grounded and sure and solid.
So think abundantly and have a powerful day.
Neither with preferences giving you at the power of love being supernatural.
And keep that moment.
Also betraying the power to attach the power to your ability of life.
Bye bye bye bye!
Bye bye bye!
Bye bye!